survio.com 2017-06-28

# Privacy Policy | Survio.com

Survio recognizes that its customers, visitors, Users, and others who use www.survio.com or other websites owned and/or operated by us (“Survio s.r.o.”) value Their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on Survio websites. We provide this Privacy Policy to help You make an informed decision on whether to use or continue using Survio websites. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated in the Terms and Conditions and is subject to Survio’s Terms of Service (TOS). Your use of the Survio sites and all of the personal information You provide on our sites remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy, as well as, to Our Terms of Service. 

Please note that any image, video, or any other content posted by Users on the Survio Surveys become published content; hence these are not considered “personally identifiable information” and therefore are not subject to this Privacy Policy.

## What information does Survio collect?

Upon registration, purchase of a product or service, and on each time You visit a Survio website or You access Your account We collect specific types of information; these are described in more detail in the following paragraphs. 

User Provided Information: Personally identifiable information (such as name and email address) that You provide to Survio when registering to Survio services or participating in various activities on the Survio sites such as uploading images and captions, uploading videos, posting messages in Our forums. 

Cookies: When You visit Survio Sites, We may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to Your computer that uniquely identifies Your browser. We use both, session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on Your hard drive after You close Your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by Your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after You close Your browser. You can reset Your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Survio Sites may not function properly if the feature “accept cookies” is disabled. 

Log Files: Log file information is automatically reported by Your browser each time You view a webpage. When You register with or view Survio Sites, Our servers automatically record certain information that Your web browser sends whenever You visit a website. These server logs may include information such as Your web request, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages and Universal Resource Locators (URL), platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of Your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify Your browser.

## The Way we Use this Information

If You submit personally identifiable information to Us through the Survio Sites, then We use Your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to You the features and functionality of the Survio Sites. 

Any personal information or content that You voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages areas and blogs, within Your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Any images, captions, videos or other content that You submit to the Survio Sites may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

We may use Your email address for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying You of major Survio Site changes or for customer service purposes). We use both Your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Survio Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionalities, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. 

We use cookies and log file information to: (a) remember information so that You will not have to re-enter it during Your visit or the next time You visit the Survio Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of Our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregated metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; (e) track Your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests; (f) diagnose or fix technical problems reported by Our Users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP; and (g) access Your information after You sign in.

## When Survio Discloses Information

We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to Our subsidiaries for the purpose of processing such information on Our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with Our Privacy Policy, and We use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state laws (such as EU Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 

It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including but not limited to, fraud, potential threats to public safety or the physical safety of any person, violations of Our Terms of Service, or as otherwise permitted by law. 

Survio also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally identifiable information that Survio believes, in good-faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Service, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend Ourselves against any Third Party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our websites, products and services, and to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Survio, Our staff, our Users or others.

## Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Survio Sites, in which case Survio may not be able to provide certain services to You. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. Please note that media files uploaded by Users to the Survio Sites cannot be removed and remain subject to Our Terms of Service. 

To protect Your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify Your identity before granting You profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of Your unique password and account information at all times.

## Our Commitment to Data Security

Survio uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of Your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information You convey to Survio, and You do so at Your own risk. Once We receive the information You submitted, Survio makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of Our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.   
If Survio learns of a security systems breach, then We may attempt to notify you electronically so that You can take appropriate protective steps. Survio may post a notice on the Our Website a security breach occurs. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw Your consent from receiving electronic notices) You should notify Our Customer Care department.

## Changes and Updates to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically and this will be reflected on the “last modified” date that is located below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, We only use Your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect at the time We received the personal information You provided. Your continued use of the Survio Sites constitutes Your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.

## Feedback

Please contact Survio with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or the Survio Sites by email to: support@survio.com

 _Last modified August 13, 2014._
